F: So if i open the application-
F: The view is kind of okay.
F: I mean, standard. Not really good yet not too bad.
F: The colour choice is fine.
F: And the button placements are not confusing.
F: Furthermore, it's easy to understand.
F: Especially for boomers who are above 40 years old that are-
F: Not exposed enough to technologies.
F: This application is fine but-
F: I think there are a few flaws. Like for example-
F: There are too much separation. If you look at-
F: "Mosque information"
F: There are 3 elements there, if i remember correctly.
F: The first one is a description about the mosque.
F: The second one is location and the third one is-
F: Pardon, i forgot the third one-
F: And i think that's-
F: I think you don't need to split those 3 elements into their own pages.
F: They're better off merged in a single page.
F: That will make it look better and we won't need to go back and forth to check on different things.
F: There's a 2nd thing i want to mention.
F: The design is too boring and monotone if compared to-
F: Other applications. So it affects the app's satisfaction.
F: Because of that, people won't be comfortable in using this app.
F: What else (app's flaws)?
F: What do you think?
F: Aldian?
A: Me?
F: Yes.
F: What do you think, Aldian?
A: Do you see the treasury section?
A: In the treasury section there's a (???) display (???) right?
F: What display?
A: The treasury display. The amount of money.
F: Yeah, and?
A: They display the treasury with a list.
A: The list is not all filled completely. It only displays this month's income.
A: It does not show previous months' incomes. Only current month's income.
F: And?
A: I think that's also one of the flaws.
T: Looks a bit useless, huh?
A: There's more (???)
F: Which is?
A: (???)
F: What? We couldn't hear you.
A: Point is-
A: There's a list (another section) where there's no filter.
F: Oh you mean like (???) list. Which is the religious lecture list
F: There are a lot of them. It would be tiring to search through if there's no filter.
A: Yeah, that oe
F: Anything else?
F: Tantyo, do you not have something to say?
T: I do.
T: Before, you said that the colour is not bad.
F: Yeah, standard but boring.
T: I think it can be better.
T: The buttons look a bit too detailed so it's not attractive
F: Not intuitive, huh?
F: So people don't really think of them as buttons.
T: Yeah, sort of.
T: And maybe not aesthetic enough.
F: Yeah, that's the right term for it.
F: Is there anything else?
T: Earlier, I tried registration for sacrifice donator. I think it didn't work.
F: It caused the app to crash, right?
T: Yes.
F: I was about to try it too but i was afraid that it will break someting.
F: So it just crashes the app?
T: Yes.
F: I want to mention something.
F: There's a menu called "Qur'an Reciter"
F: It's about qur'an readers, right?
F: But when i open it, the app leads me to a site. In my opinion, this is bad because-
F: Based on safety, it's-
F: It's a bit risky. Because if the user gets attacked, the app maker won't be responsible.
F: There's a chance that the site can't be trusted. So this must be fixed.
F: Anything else?
F: Aldian, do you have an opinion (on this app)?
A: (Disconnected)
F: So, from what i see-
F: Hold on, let me check again.
F: Oh, right. There's this sacrifice donator registration that keeps failing.
T: That's what i mentioned earlier, Farhan.
T: I already mentioned that.
F: The donation?
T: Yes.
F: No, wait. That was about the crash.
F: You were mentioning about checking it. So now, when i'm trying the registration part, it keeps failing even though i gave the right input.
T: I think the cleric schedule in the friday prayer section is awkward.
F: Oh the-
F: Pardon?
T: (Disconnected)
T: I was confused on what does M and H mean (in the cleric schedule).
T: The meaning doesn't come naturally. You have to-
F: Oh, you have to think a bit harder on it, right?
F: I thought so too. There was a moment where i thought M means month.
F: When i checked again. "There's January but why is there M 3"
F: Turns out, there are Anno Domini and Hijriyah.
F: This schedule format can really confuse people.
F: Do you have anymore to say?
F: Aldian?
A: (Lost connection)
F: Based on our interview with Eric, designs must not make the users think too much. It should be easy for the users.
F: And i think the schedules are zoomed pictures. It would be better if-
F: They're not pictures. But part of the application. In the form of calendar.
F: Something like that.
T: You mean like-
F: They look like imported pictures, right? I mean, not natural like calendars in html.
T: You mean they look like pictures and not formatted schedules?
F: Yes, like a hard-inputted image.
F: Not like in a formatted way in the code.
T: Anymore?
F: Any other opinions? I think that's all.
T: You sure?
F: You found another flawed part?
T: Not really. But i feel like-
T: Something is missing. But-
T: Never mind. I think we've mentioned all of them.
F: Hmm. Yeah, i think that's all for the flaws in the app's user interactions.